<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>functional-programming on The Unhandled Exception Podcast</title>
    <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/tags/functional-programming/</link>
    <description>Recent content in functional-programming on The Unhandled Exception Podcast</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/tags/functional-programming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Episode 10: F# and Functional Programming</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0010-fsharp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0010-fsharp/</guid>
      <description>In this group episode I was joined by Scott Wlaschin, Isaac Abraham, and Ian Russell - to talk all about F#! This is .NET&amp;rsquo;s functional programming language, and we discussed functional programming, and the benefits of using a functional programming language like F#, whilst also comparing it to other languages like C#.
  Guests&#39; social links  Ian Russell: Twitter, LinkedIn Isaac Abraham: Twitter, LinkedIn Scott Wlaschin: Twitter, LinkedIn  Links from the show  F# for fun and profit (Scott&amp;rsquo;s website) Ian&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Introduction To Functional Programming In F#&amp;rdquo; blog post series Isaac&amp;rsquo;s book: &amp;ldquo;Get Programming with F#&amp;quot; Scott&amp;rsquo;s book: &amp;ldquo;Domain Modeling Made Functional&amp;rdquo; Dan&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Writing More Succinct C#&amp;rdquo; blog post C# code-snippet Dan referred to when talking about using LINQ on a single object Nancy Framework Carter API Endpoints Diamond Kata:  Diamond Kata - TDD with only property-based tests Diamond Kata in F#   Book: &amp;ldquo;Stylish F#&amp;rdquo; by Kit Eason (@kitlovesfsharp) Blog post: &amp;ldquo;Ten reasons not to use a statically typed functional programming language&amp;rdquo; (&amp;ldquo;Like most programmers, I’m naturally conservative and I dislike learning new things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 9: Functional Programming in C# with Simon Painter</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0009-simonpainter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0009-simonpainter/</guid>
      <description>For this very first episode of 2021, I was joined by Simon Painter to talk all about Functional Programming in C#! We spoke about functional concepts, plus terms such as Options, Maybes, and even tried to explain what a Monad is! As usual, there were a few tangents, and we also touched on topics such as React, TDD, and much more!
  Links from the show  Simon&amp;rsquo;s social links:  Twitter Website   Book: Functional Programming in C# by Enrico Buonanno Recording of Simon&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Functional Programming in C# talk (thanks to .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 2: Derek Comartin - CQRS, MediatR, and more!</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0002-derekcomartin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0002-derekcomartin/</guid>
      <description>In this second episode, I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to welcome Derek Comartin (also known as CodeOpinion) onto the show to talk about CQRS and MediatR! We ended up recording over two different sessions and covered lots of different topics, including functional programming and remote working.
  Links from the show  Derek on Twitter Derek&amp;rsquo;s blog Derek&amp;rsquo;s YouTube channel MediatR language-ext functional C# library Dan&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Writing More Succinct C#&amp;rdquo; blog post Simon Painter&amp;rsquo;s Functional Programming in C# talk LINQPad (from devtips) Dan&amp;rsquo;s LINQPad Tips and Tricks blog post series  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
