<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Security on The Unhandled Exception Podcast</title>
    <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/tags/security/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Security on The Unhandled Exception Podcast</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/tags/security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Episode 47: Application Security - with Tanya Janca</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0047-applicationsecurity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0047-applicationsecurity/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode, I was joined by &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/shehackspurple&#34;&gt;Tanya Janca&lt;/a&gt; to chat about Application Security (or AppSec for short!). We chatted about various topics - from security topics and training, to her book and online community, to public speaking!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Tanya is the founder and CEO at &lt;a href=&#34;https://community.wehackpurple.com/&#34;&gt;We Hack Purple&lt;/a&gt;, which is an online learning academy, community and weekly podcast that revolves around teaching everyone to create secure software. She&amp;rsquo;s also the Director of Developer Relations at &lt;a href=&#34;https://brightsec.com/&#34;&gt;Bright&lt;/a&gt;, and best-selling author of the book &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.co.uk/Alice-Bob-Learn-Application-Security/dp/1119687357&#34;&gt;Alice and Bob Learn Application Security&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 8: Identity with Christos Matskas</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0008-identitywithchristosmatskas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0008-identitywithchristosmatskas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this last episode of the year, I was joined by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.twitter.com/christosmatskas&#34;&gt;Christos Matskas&lt;/a&gt; to talk all about Identity! Christos is the Program Manager for the Microsoft Identity Platform, so obviously the conversation was slightly biased towards AzureAD and B2C as an identity provider - but we also tried to cover some common identity topics, and demystify terminology such as OAuth, OpenID Connect, scopes, claims, and more! We even went a bit &lt;em&gt;off-piste&lt;/em&gt; at the end and chatted about public speaking, languages (not programming languages), and even touched on speed reading!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
