<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Terraform on The Unhandled Exception Podcast</title>
    <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/tags/terraform/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Terraform on The Unhandled Exception Podcast</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/tags/terraform/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Episode 61: Platform Engineering and IaC - with Shahid Iqbal</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0061-platformengineering/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0061-platformengineering/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined for a second time by Shahid Iqbal, this time to chat about Platform Engineering and Infrastructure as Code! We discussed what Platform Engineering means, and also different IaC tools. And Shahid&amp;rsquo;s undying love for Pulumi! 😂
Shahid is a Principal Platform Architect at Auror based in Auckland NZ, and is also an Azure MVP.
   Shahid&amp;rsquo;s social links  Twitter LinkedIn Blog  Links from the show  Terraform Pulumi Past episode where we talked about Kubernetes Episode on OTel with Martin Thwaites Article on Terraform licence change OpenTofu   If you&amp;rsquo;re enjoying the podcast, please remember to subscribe and share this episode with your friends and colleagues!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 13: DevOps with Dushyant</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0013-devopswithdushyant/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0013-devopswithdushyant/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by good friend and ex-colleague, Dushyant Priyadarshee to chat about devops! We covered a lot of ground, from what devops is, to infrastructure as code deployments, to exams and certifications! Dushyant is a Senior Platform Engineer at NewDay.
  Links from the show Dushyant&amp;rsquo;s links  Blog Twitter LinkedIn NewDay (workplace)  Other links from the show  Terraform Terraform CDK Pulumi Bicep Terratest TFSec Azure DevOps Azure ARM Templates Azure DevOps &amp;ldquo;name&amp;rdquo; Twitter Poll GitHub Actions Microsoft Learn Microsoft Exams/Certifications MeasureUp  DevTip links  Daily Coding Problem The Phoenix Project book The Unicorn Project Notion  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
