<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Unhandled Exception Podcast</title>
    <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Unhandled Exception Podcast</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Episode 19: Blazor with Chris Sainty</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0019-blazor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0019-blazor/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was thrilled to be joined by Chris Sainty to chat all about Blazor! Blazor is a new .NET technology allowing you to build SPA-like frontend web UIs in C#! Very focused on developer productivity and componentisation - Blazor is certainly going to become my go-to for frontends moving forward! And chatting with Chris in this episode, has shown me even more reasons why Blazor is becoming so immensely popular!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 18: Mutation Testing in .NET with Stefan Pölz</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0018-mutationtesting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0018-mutationtesting/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was thrilled to be joined by Stefan Pölz to chat about Mutation Testing! I had seen a lightning talk by Stefan last year about this, and was fascinated by the concept. So it was great to have him on the show to chat about it!
  Links from the show Stefan&amp;rsquo;s Social Links  Twitter LinkedIn Github  Other links from the show  Stryker.NET (ie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 17: TDD with Ian Cooper</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0017-tddwithiancooper/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0017-tddwithiancooper/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Ian Cooper to chat about Test Driven Development (TDD)! We discussed pain points that a lot of people hit when attempting to do TDD, and how to avoid them.
  Links from the show Ian&amp;rsquo;s Social Links  Twitter LinkedIn Github  Other links from the show  Ian&amp;rsquo;s Presentations on Github Ian&amp;rsquo;s talk - &amp;lsquo;TDD - Where did it all go wrong?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 16: Learning and Self Development with James World</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0016-learningwithjamesworld/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0016-learningwithjamesworld/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by James World to chat about learning! We covered an incredible amount in this episode - from certifications, to books and reading, interviews, what it means to be a senior developer, and much much more!
  Links from the show James&#39; Links  Twitter LinkedIn (please include a note in your connection request so you stand out from the recruiter bots! Maybe a book recommendation?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 15: C#9 Source Generators with Jason Bock</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0015-sourcegeneratorswithjasonbock/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0015-sourcegeneratorswithjasonbock/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Jason Bock to chat about the new C#9 source generators! Writing code that writes code! We covered a ton of content, covering Source Generators, the Compiler API, Syntax Trees, Semantic Models, Expression Trees, and much much more!
  Links from the show Jason&amp;rsquo;s Links  Twitter Blog Github YouTube  Jason&amp;rsquo;s books  Metaprogramming in .NET Applied .NET Attributes CIL Programming: Under the Hood of .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 14: Spectre Console and Cake with Patrik Svensson</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0014-patriksvensson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0014-patriksvensson/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Patrik Svensson, creator of both the Cake Build System, and a .NET library called Spectre.Console. We mostly chatted about the Spectre Console library, which adds AMAZING functionality to .NET console apps (grid, charts, images, and much more!). We also touched on Cake and Cake Frosting.
  Links from the show Patriks links  Blog Twitter LinkedIn  Links from the show  Spectre.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 13: DevOps with Dushyant</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0013-devopswithdushyant/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0013-devopswithdushyant/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by good friend and ex-colleague, Dushyant Priyadarshee to chat about devops! We covered a lot of ground, from what devops is, to infrastructure as code deployments, to exams and certifications! Dushyant is a Senior Platform Engineer at NewDay.
  Links from the show Dushyant&amp;rsquo;s links  Blog Twitter LinkedIn NewDay (workplace)  Other links from the show  Terraform Terraform CDK Pulumi Bicep Terratest TFSec Azure DevOps Azure ARM Templates Azure DevOps &amp;ldquo;name&amp;rdquo; Twitter Poll GitHub Actions Microsoft Learn Microsoft Exams/Certifications MeasureUp  DevTip links  Daily Coding Problem The Phoenix Project book The Unicorn Project Notion  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 12: Kentico Kontent Headless CMS and JAMStack - with Matt Nield</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0012-mattnield/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0012-mattnield/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by good friend Matt Nield, who also co-runs the .NET Oxford user group with me. We chatted about the Kentico Kontent headless CMS, static websites and the JAMStack - plus much more!
  Links from the show Matt&amp;rsquo;s links  Matt&amp;rsquo;s website Matt on Twitter  Kentico  Kentico main website Kentico Kontent Kentico Xperience (previously Kentico EMS): Kentico Kontent extended 3-month trial offer from Matt  Other links from the show  JAMStack HttpClient Interceptor LINQPad Matt&amp;rsquo;s YouTube video on using Kentico Kontent with LINQPad Statiq .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 11: LINQPad with Joseph Albahari</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0011-linqpad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0011-linqpad/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Joe Albahari, author of one of my favourite software development tools - LINQPad! This is a tool that I use on a daily basis, and it saves me so much time! So I especially enjoyed chatting with Joe about the many features of LINQPad, his experiences when developing it, and also future plans.
  Links from the show  LINQPad Joe&amp;rsquo;s website Joe/LINQPad on Twitter LINQPad Tips and Tricks blog post series: Part1, Part2, Part 3 Writing a Neural Net from Scratch talk Pushing C# to the limit talk (alarm clock reference) .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 10: F# and Functional Programming</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0010-fsharp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0010-fsharp/</guid>
      <description>In this group episode I was joined by Scott Wlaschin, Isaac Abraham, and Ian Russell - to talk all about F#! This is .NET&amp;rsquo;s functional programming language, and we discussed functional programming, and the benefits of using a functional programming language like F#, whilst also comparing it to other languages like C#.
  Guests&#39; social links  Ian Russell: Twitter, LinkedIn Isaac Abraham: Twitter, LinkedIn Scott Wlaschin: Twitter, LinkedIn  Links from the show  F# for fun and profit (Scott&amp;rsquo;s website) Ian&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Introduction To Functional Programming In F#&amp;rdquo; blog post series Isaac&amp;rsquo;s book: &amp;ldquo;Get Programming with F#&amp;quot; Scott&amp;rsquo;s book: &amp;ldquo;Domain Modeling Made Functional&amp;rdquo; Dan&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Writing More Succinct C#&amp;rdquo; blog post C# code-snippet Dan referred to when talking about using LINQ on a single object Nancy Framework Carter API Endpoints Diamond Kata:  Diamond Kata - TDD with only property-based tests Diamond Kata in F#   Book: &amp;ldquo;Stylish F#&amp;rdquo; by Kit Eason (@kitlovesfsharp) Blog post: &amp;ldquo;Ten reasons not to use a statically typed functional programming language&amp;rdquo; (&amp;ldquo;Like most programmers, I’m naturally conservative and I dislike learning new things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 9: Functional Programming in C# with Simon Painter</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0009-simonpainter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0009-simonpainter/</guid>
      <description>For this very first episode of 2021, I was joined by Simon Painter to talk all about Functional Programming in C#! We spoke about functional concepts, plus terms such as Options, Maybes, and even tried to explain what a Monad is! As usual, there were a few tangents, and we also touched on topics such as React, TDD, and much more!
  Links from the show  Simon&amp;rsquo;s social links:  Twitter Website   Book: Functional Programming in C# by Enrico Buonanno Recording of Simon&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Functional Programming in C# talk (thanks to .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 8: Identity with Christos Matskas</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0008-identitywithchristosmatskas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0008-identitywithchristosmatskas/</guid>
      <description>In this last episode of the year, I was joined by Christos Matskas to talk all about Identity! Christos is the Program Manager for the Microsoft Identity Platform, so obviously the conversation was slightly biased towards AzureAD and B2C as an identity provider - but we also tried to cover some common identity topics, and demystify terminology such as OAuth, OpenID Connect, scopes, claims, and more! We even went a bit off-piste at the end and chatted about public speaking, languages (not programming languages), and even touched on speed reading!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 7: WSL2 with Stuart Leeks</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0006-stuartleeks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0006-stuartleeks/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Stuart Leeks to chat all about WSL2, and his new book, WSL 2 Tips, Tricks, and Techniques! We also covered plenty of other topics, such as public speaking, Windows Terminal, standing desks, and much more! Stuart is a Principal Software Development Engineer at Microsoft.
  Links from the show  Stuart&amp;rsquo;s social links:  Twitter Blog GitHub   THE BOOK! WSL2 homepage Dr Michelle Dickinson:  @NanogirlLabs on Twitter Public Speaking Skills for Quiet People How to Rock the Stage (with Dr James Whittaker)   Stuart&amp;rsquo;s WSL2 .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 6: The DDD Conferences</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0006-ddd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0006-ddd/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by five awesome guests to chat all about the DDD conferences! This was such a fun episode, where we chatted about both organising and speaking at the DDD conferences, plus a few other bits and bats along the way!
  Guests  Jess White Paul Michaels Pete Gallagher Simon Painter Stuart Lang  Links from the show  Wikipedia page about the DDD conferences DDD Day DDD East Midlands blog DDD South West DDD North DDD East Anglia DDD Scotland Event registration for DDD on the 12th Dec Ian Johnson&amp;rsquo;s sketch notes Musical instrument photo taken at end Paul&amp;rsquo;s MiniHack meetup mentioned in intro Dan&amp;rsquo;s DDD-related blog posts:  2017: &amp;ldquo;Fun at DDDSW in Bristol!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 5: Kubernetes with Shahid Iqbal</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0005-shahidiqbal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0005-shahidiqbal/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Shahid Iqbal to chat about Kubernetes. We covered containers in general, Docker, Docker-Compose, Kubernetes, Helm, Istio, and much more! Shahid is a Microsoft MVP and user-group organiser, specialising in Azure and Kubernetes.
  Links from the show  Shahid on Twitter Shahid&amp;rsquo;s blog Kubernetes Azure AKS Google GKE Amazon EKS Helm Istio Project Tye KataCoda &amp;lsquo;Deploying blog on Kubernetes&amp;rsquo; meme ZoomIt Chris O&amp;rsquo;Dell talk on &amp;lsquo;How to get your submission accepted at NDC London&amp;rsquo;  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 4: Pete Gallagher</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0004-petegallagher/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0004-petegallagher/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Pete Gallagher - Microsoft MVP, Pluralsight author, speaker, user-group organiser, and huge fan of IoT devices and STEM. We had great fun chatted for over an hour about various topics - mostly themed around technologies helping kids get into coding - but with many tangents thrown into the mix!
  Links from the show  Pete on Twitter Pete&amp;rsquo;s blog Scratch Tinkercad Microbit Kit MakeCode MakeCode Extensions MakeCode Arcade Raspberry Pi Simulator MX Chip Simulator ML For Kids Lobe AI AZ220 IoT Exam IoT Docs and Learn Sense Hat Simulator MicroBit: MCP23s17 I/O Expander Source Code AstroPi .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 3: Steve Gordon</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0003-stevegordon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0003-stevegordon/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I had a fascinating chat with Steve Gordon. We covered tons of topics - from his experience in being a Pluralsight author, to performance, productivity, organising user-groups, public speaking, audio editing, and much more!
  Links from the show   Steve&amp;rsquo;s social and content links:
 Twitter Blog Pluralsight YouTube    User-group links and mentioned events:
 .NET South East (Steve&amp;rsquo;s user-group) MK.NET meetup with Steve on the 18th Scott Hanselman&amp;rsquo;s talk at .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 2: Derek Comartin - CQRS, MediatR, and more!</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0002-derekcomartin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0002-derekcomartin/</guid>
      <description>In this second episode, I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to welcome Derek Comartin (also known as CodeOpinion) onto the show to talk about CQRS and MediatR! We ended up recording over two different sessions and covered lots of different topics, including functional programming and remote working.
  Links from the show  Derek on Twitter Derek&amp;rsquo;s blog Derek&amp;rsquo;s YouTube channel MediatR language-ext functional C# library Dan&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Writing More Succinct C#&amp;rdquo; blog post Simon Painter&amp;rsquo;s Functional Programming in C# talk LINQPad (from devtips) Dan&amp;rsquo;s LINQPad Tips and Tricks blog post series  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 1: Hello World!</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0001-helloworld/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0001-helloworld/</guid>
      <description>In this very first episode, I introduce the podcast and what it&amp;rsquo;s all about! This is a short 6-minute episode talking about the focus of the podcast, who I am, and also a bit about .NET Oxford.
  Links from the show  Dan&amp;rsquo;s blog Dan on Twitter .NET Oxford .NET Oxford Slack Azure Oxford  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/pages/about/</guid>
      <description>About page coming soon.
For more information about me, see the about page on my blog.
The best way to get in touch with me is via Twitter - my DMs are open.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guest FAQ</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/pages/guest-faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/pages/guest-faq/</guid>
      <description>Ever wondered what&amp;rsquo;s involved when being a guest on a podcast? Below are a few key points that I tend to mention to each guest. I thought I&amp;rsquo;d consolidate them here for quick reference&amp;hellip;
The podcast is not live! I do a lot of editing afterwards, and it&amp;rsquo;s easy to chop bits out whilst editing. If you need to pause and think about how you&amp;rsquo;re going to answer a question - that&amp;rsquo;s fine - I chop that pause out.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
