<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Unhandled Exception Podcast</title>
    <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Unhandled Exception Podcast</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Episode 6: The DDD Conferences</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0006-ddd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0006-ddd/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by five awesome guests to chat all about the DDD conferences! This was such a fun episode, where we chatted about both organising and speaking at the DDD conferences, plus a few other bits and bats along the way!
  Guests  Jess White Paul Michaels Pete Gallagher Simon Painter Stuart Lang  Links from the show  Wikipedia page about the DDD conferences DDD Day DDD East Midlands blog DDD South West DDD North DDD East Anglia DDD Scotland Event registration for DDD on the 12th Dec Ian Johnson&amp;rsquo;s sketch notes Musical instrument photo taken at end Dan&amp;rsquo;s DDD-related blog posts:  2017: &amp;ldquo;Fun at DDDSW in Bristol!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 5: Kubernetes with Shahid Iqbal</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0005-shahidiqbal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0005-shahidiqbal/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Shahid Iqbal to chat about Kubernetes. We covered containers in general, Docker, Docker-Compose, Kubernetes, Helm, Istio, and much more! Shahid is a Microsoft MVP and user-group organiser, specialising in Azure and Kubernetes.
  Links from the show  Shahid on Twitter Shahid&amp;rsquo;s blog Kubernetes Azure AKS Google GKE Amazon EKS Helm Istio Project Tye KataCoda &amp;lsquo;Deploying blog on Kubernetes&amp;rsquo; meme ZoomIt Chris O&amp;rsquo;Dell talk on &amp;lsquo;How to get your submission accepted at NDC London&amp;rsquo;  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 4: Pete Gallagher</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0004-petegallagher/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0004-petegallagher/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Pete Gallagher - Microsoft MVP, Pluralsight author, speaker, user-group organiser, and huge fan of IoT devices and STEM. We had great fun chatted for over an hour about various topics - mostly themed around technologies helping kids get into coding - but with many tangents thrown into the mix!
  Links from the show  Pete on Twitter Pete&amp;rsquo;s blog Scratch Tinkercad Microbit Kit MakeCode MakeCode Extensions MakeCode Arcade Raspberry Pi Simulator MX Chip Simulator ML For Kids Lobe AI AZ220 IoT Exam IoT Docs and Learn Sense Hat Simulator MicroBit: MCP23s17 I/O Expander Source Code AstroPi .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 3: Steve Gordon</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0003-stevegordon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0003-stevegordon/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I had a fascinating chat with Steve Gordon. We covered tons of topics - from his experience in being a Pluralsight author, to performance, productivity, organising user-groups, public speaking, audio editing, and much more!
  Links from the show   Steve&amp;rsquo;s social and content links:
 Twitter Blog Pluralsight YouTube    User-group links and mentioned events:
 .NET South East (Steve&amp;rsquo;s user-group) MK.NET meetup with Steve on the 18th Scott Hanselman&amp;rsquo;s talk at .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 2: Derek Comartin - CQRS, MediatR, and more!</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0002-derekcomartin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0002-derekcomartin/</guid>
      <description>In this second episode, I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to welcome Derek Comartin (also known as CodeOpinion) onto the show to talk about CQRS and MediatR! We ended up recording over two different sessions and covered lots of different topics, including functional programming and remote working.
  Links from the show  Derek on Twitter Derek&amp;rsquo;s blog Derek&amp;rsquo;s YouTube channel MediatR language-ext functional C# library Dan&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Writing More Succinct C#&amp;rdquo; blog post Simon Painter&amp;rsquo;s Functional Programming in C# talk LINQPad (from devtips) Dan&amp;rsquo;s LINQPad Tips and Tricks blog post series  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/pages/about/</guid>
      <description>About page coming soon. For more information about me, see the about page on my blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 1: Hello World!</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0001-helloworld/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0001-helloworld/</guid>
      <description>In this very first episode, I introduce the podcast and what it&amp;rsquo;s all about! This is a short 6-minute episode talking about the focus of the podcast, who I am, and also a bit about .NET Oxford.
  Links from the show  Dan&amp;rsquo;s blog Dan on Twitter .NET Oxford .NET Oxford Slack Azure Oxford  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
