<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Unhandled Exception Podcast</title>
    <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Unhandled Exception Podcast</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Episode 43: Docker Demystified</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0043-dockerdemystified/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0043-dockerdemystified/</guid>
      <description>This episode was a solo episode where I try my best to &amp;ldquo;demystify&amp;rdquo; Docker! A difficult task over an audio podcast, so hopefully it&amp;rsquo;s !digestible! I cover the following topics&amp;hellip;
 What are containers and images? Container registries Use cases for containers Interacting with Docker Docker Compose Volumes Building your own images Image layer caching Multi-stage Dockerfiles About Container Orchestrators Using Docker for local development    Dan&amp;rsquo;s social links  Twitter LinkedIn Blog  Links from the show  Docker Docker docs Docker Compose docs Kubernetes Blog post: Switching to multi-stage Docker files Video: Integration Testing ASP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 42: The Unlikely Success of a Copy Paste Developer - with Iris Classon</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0042-irisclasson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0042-irisclasson/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Iris Classon to chat all about her book - The Unlikely Success of a Copy Paste Developer. The book is a very fun, light-hearted, fictional novel about a software developer called Leo, and a range of very interesting characters Leo has to work with. I&amp;rsquo;ve recently read the book, and thoroughly enjoyed it. As a software developer, a lot of the stories are very relatable!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 41: OpenTelemetry - with Martin Thwaites</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0041-opentelemetry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0041-opentelemetry/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Martin Thwaites from Honeycomb to chat about OpenTelemetry. OpenTelemetry (or OTel) standardises metrics, logs, and traces - allowing different systems and languages to be able to write telemetry data in a common format and be understood by any visualisation UIs that support it. This is becoming widely adopted, meaning that with minor changes to your applications - you can ship off telemetry to various combinations of providers, giving you much more choice and flexibility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 40: Demystifying Messaging in Azure - with Sean Feldman</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0040-azuremessaging/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0040-azuremessaging/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Sean Feldman to chat all about messaging in Azure! Starting off explaining why you&amp;rsquo;d want to use messaging in your solutions. Then explaining the difference between different types of messaging - eg. pub/sub, event streaming, etc. Then going through discussing all the different Azure services that relate to messaging.
Sean Feldman is a consulting Solutions Architect and an Azure MVP. He likes tinkering with various Azure-related services and is in seventh heaven when cloud and distributed technologies are combined.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 39: Windows Terminal - with Kayla Cinnamon</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0039-windowsterminal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0039-windowsterminal/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was thrilled to be joined by Kayla Cinnamon to chat about the Windows Terminal! I&amp;rsquo;m a huge fan of WT, and use it daily - so it was an honour to have Kayla on to chat about it! Kayla is a Program Manager at Microsoft, Delivering Windows Terminal and Cascadia Code. She&amp;rsquo;s also the Host of Windows Wednesday, and works on the Windows developer experience.
  Kayla&amp;rsquo;s social links  Twitter LinkedIn  Links from the show  Windows Terminal on GitHub Windows Terminal Promo video PoshGit TerminalSplash.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 38: .NET MAUI, IoT, and Handy the bionic Arm - with Clifford Agius</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0038-cliffordagius/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0038-cliffordagius/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Clifford Agius to chat about both .NET MAUI, and also developing for IoT. (These were separate topics - not specifically IoT on MAUI). Clifford is an airline pilot who&amp;rsquo;s also a freelance .NET developer who regularly blogs and speaks at conferences around the world!
MAUI (Multi-platform App UI) is a new .NET framework for building multi-platform apps - both mobile (iOS/Android) and desktop (macOS/Windows) using C# and XAML in a single codebase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 37: Microsoft Build 2022</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0037-build/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0037-build/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft have just had their annual Build conference - which comes with a whole host of exciting announcements and discussions about hot programming topics in the Microsoft developer space. And each year, I long for a podcast episode to come out straight after Build, overviewing them! Well, this year - this podcast aims to do just that! In this episode, I was joined by both Scott Hunter and Gaurav Seth to chat about various topics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 36: Andrew Lock - ASP.NET, Blogging, Kubernetes, and more!</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0036-andrewlock/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0036-andrewlock/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was honoured to be joined by Andrew Lock, who is probably best known for his amazing &amp;lsquo;must-subscribe&amp;rsquo; blog - andrewlock.net. He&amp;rsquo;s also the author of the Manning ebook, ASP.NET Core in Action, Second Edition. We covered a lot in this episode - from the different flavours of ASP.NET, to Kubernetes, Blazor, gRPC, testing, Minimal API, MediatR&amp;hellip; and more!
  Guests&#39; social links  Blog Twitter LinkedIn Github  Links from the show  Andrew&amp;rsquo;s book - ASP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 35: MiniHack</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0035-minihack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0035-minihack/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Paul Michaels and Kev Smith, to chat about their monthly online meetup they both run.
MiniHack is an online tech-agnostic monthly meetup, where teams of between 3 and 6 people compete to produce the best solution to a given problem. In their own words - &amp;ldquo;Where we meet monthly to come up with cool solutions to pointless problems&amp;rdquo;.
  Guests&#39; social links  Paul on Twitter Paul on LinkedIn Kev on Twitter Kev on LinkedIn  Links from the show  MiniHack website MiniHack on GitHub MiniHack on Twitter Promo video Brain**** programming language  Dev Picks  Tech Community Calendar - by Lee Englestone .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 34: Geeking out on .NET with Nick Chapsas</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0034-nickchapsas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0034-nickchapsas/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was thrilled to be joined by Nick Chapsas! If you&amp;rsquo;re a .NET developer - then his YouTube channel is an absolute must! Given all the amazing topics he covers on his channel - it would have been a shame to just chat with him about a single topic! So we decided to do a few lightning topics instead! Here&amp;rsquo;s what we geeked out on&amp;hellip;
 .NET 6 Minimal API The outdated opinion of some non .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 33: Razor Pages with Mike Brind</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0033-razorpages/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0033-razorpages/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Mike Brind to chat about ASP.NET Core Razor Pages. We also spoke about his Manning MEAP book, ASP.NET Core Razor Pages in Action.
  Mike&amp;rsquo;s social links  Twitter Github Blog LinkedIn  Links from the show  Razor Pages on Microsoft Docs Mike&amp;rsquo;s Book: ASP.NET Core Razor Pages in Action (Manning 35% discount code for any of their books: podunhandled21) learnrazorpages.com Blog post from Andrew Lock about not replacing View Components with Razor Components in Razor Pages  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 32: Technical Leadership - with Jess White</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0032-jesswhite/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0032-jesswhite/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Jess White to chat about technical leadership and how to support teams and manage people. Jess provides tons of advice and insights into what makes teams both happy and productive.
  Jess&amp;rsquo;s social links  Twitter Github Blog YouTube LinkedIn  Links from the show  Jess&amp;rsquo;s talk at .NET South West Past podcast episode with Jess - the group DDD episode DDD East Midlands School of Code Makers Academy .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 31: MassTransit and Open Source - with Chris Patterson</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0031-masstransit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0031-masstransit/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Chris Patterson to chat about the open-source distributed messaging framework, MassTransit. We also spoke about open-source, event-driven architecture, docker, k8s, testing, Rider, and more!
  Chris&amp;rsquo;s social links  Twitter Github YouTube  Links from the show  MassTransit MassTransit Discord RabbitMQ Azure Service Bus Apache Kafka Azure Event Hub Kubernetes Istio Linkerd JetBrains Rider Visual Studio Live Share JetBrains Code With Me Past podcast episode re.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 30: Developer Productivity with (me!) Dan Clarke</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0030-developerproductivity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0030-developerproductivity/</guid>
      <description>Developer productivity is something I&amp;rsquo;ve been really interested in for quite a few years. So I decided, rather than having a guest on for this topic - it&amp;rsquo;s one I wanted to cover myself. So in this first episode of the year - I&amp;rsquo;ve gone solo, and talk about the things I find have made a big difference to my productivity over the years. Also why I think this term &amp;ldquo;10x developer&amp;rdquo; is a big understatement!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 29: Snapshot Testing with Simon Cropp</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0029-snapshottesting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0029-snapshottesting/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Simon Cropp to chat about a form of testing called Snapshot testing! Simon is the author of Verify, which is a library that I&amp;rsquo;m quickly discovering is going to save me a HUGE amount of time when writing tests in dotnet! We chatted about snapshot testing in general; the various helper extensions that Verify has, which adds support for lots of different technologies; and also about testing in general.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 28: UX with Jessica Engström</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0028-uxwithjessicaengstrom/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0028-uxwithjessicaengstrom/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Jessica Engström to chat about UX! A topic that most developers (myself included) need to be more aware of when building UIs! Jessica is also a fellow podcast host, co-hosting the awesome Coding After Work podcast!
  Jess&amp;rsquo;s social links  Twitter LinkedIn Github Blog  Links from the show  Coding After Work:  Podcast Twitch YouTube   What is Aphantasia?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 27: Visual Studio 2022 - with Kendra Havens</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0027-kendrahavens/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0027-kendrahavens/</guid>
      <description>Not long to go until the release of both .NET 6 and Visual Studio 2022! But if you can&amp;rsquo;t wait that long - the preview releases of both can be downloaded right now! In this episode, I was joined by Kendra Havens to chat about what&amp;rsquo;s new and coming! Kendra is a Program Manager on the .NET and Visual Studio team, and we also chatted a bit in this episode about what software development is like internally at Microsoft, and learn that Microsoft face the same struggles as most other companies!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 26: Event Sourcing and Event Driven Architecture - with Callum Linington</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0026-eventsourcing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0026-eventsourcing/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Callum Linington to chat about Event Sourcing! Events over time are how the world works - so shouldn&amp;rsquo;t we be leveraging that in our architectures? As quite often happens, we also went on one or two tangents, and covered a ton of other related including MediatR, CQRS, F#, DDD, Rx, Redux, and more!
  Callum&amp;rsquo;s social links  Twitter LinkedIn Github  Links from the show  EventStore Apache Kafka Video: Greg Young — A Decade of DDD, CQRS, Event Sourcing MediatR Redux Rx Callum&amp;rsquo;s Liaison library Video: &amp;lsquo;Reaqtor&amp;rsquo; - Endjin&amp;rsquo;s Rx at scale talk at .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 25: NDepend with Patrick Smacchia</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0025-ndepend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0025-ndepend/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Patrick Smacchia, all the way from the beautiful island of Mauritius, to chat all about NDepend! An amazing tool for analysing .NET projects and displaying tons of useful information to help improve code quality. From scanning for code quality issues, to showing plenty of dependency graphs and code visualisations.
  Links from the show  NDepend NDepend use cases NDepend blog Patrick&amp;rsquo;s WSL2 blog post mentioned in his dev tip LINQPad  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 24: Dependency Injection in .NET with Steve Collins</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0024-stevecollins/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0024-stevecollins/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Steve Collins to chat all about dependency injection in .NET. We (well, Steve!) demystified terms such as dependency inversion and inversion of control containers, and then delved into the world of dependency injection in .NET, covering scopes, and much more&amp;hellip;
  Steve&amp;rsquo;s bio Steve Collins is an independent software developer/architect with over 25 years of experience in the industry. He started developing in early &amp;rsquo;80s on ZX Spectrum, self-taught BASIC and Z80 Assembler.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 23: Git - with Jesse Liberty and James World</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0023-git/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0023-git/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Jesse Liberty and James World to chat about a topic I&amp;rsquo;m also personally very passionate about - the Git source control system.
Jesse is a fellow podcast host, as well as an author of a book about Git.
James is a Solution Architect who has done many a talk on Git and likes to delve a bit deeper into what goes on under the hood (as you&amp;rsquo;ll see in this episode!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 22: Jetbrains Rider, and Code With Me</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0022-rider/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0022-rider/</guid>
      <description>Everyone who knows me, knows I&amp;rsquo;m a massive fan of Jetbrains Rider! So it was about time we had an episode on it! In this episode, I was joined by both Maarten Balliauw and Kirill Skrygan to chat all about it. We discussed the Rider architecture, Code With Me, Remote Development; and also the awesome power of keyboard shortcuts!
  Maarten Balliauw&amp;rsquo;s Bio Maarten Balliauw loves building web and cloud apps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 21: Bicep with Alex Frankel</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0021-bicep/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0021-bicep/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Alex Frankel to chat about Azure Bicep! Bicep is a new DSL that transpiles down to native ARM templates. Except that it greatly improved upon the very hard to read and write ARM templates, making Infrastructure as Code in Azure a far nicer user experience. We delved into the Bicep language, the tooling, a bit of the history - and even geeked out a bit on how awesome .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 20: Mark Rendle&#39;s Stream of Consciousness</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0020-markrendle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0020-markrendle/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Mark Rendle to chat about his experiences live-coding/streaming on Twitch! Warning: We went on a lot of tangents during the conversation! It&amp;rsquo;s all good though - as they were all awesome tangents! We not only talked about streaming, but also Blazor, C#, Unity, the rate of tech advancement, teaching kids to code, and much more!
  Mark&amp;rsquo;s Bio Mark Rendle decided he wanted to be a programmer when he was 10, became a professional programmer when he was 16, and is still a programmer 30 years later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 19: Blazor with Chris Sainty</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0019-blazor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0019-blazor/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was thrilled to be joined by Chris Sainty to chat all about Blazor! Blazor is a new .NET technology allowing you to build SPA-like frontend web UIs in C#! Very focused on developer productivity and componentisation - Blazor is certainly going to become my go-to for frontends moving forward! And chatting with Chris in this episode, has shown me even more reasons why Blazor is becoming so immensely popular!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 18: Mutation Testing in .NET with Stefan Pölz</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0018-mutationtesting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0018-mutationtesting/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was thrilled to be joined by Stefan Pölz to chat about Mutation Testing! I had seen a lightning talk by Stefan last year about this, and was fascinated by the concept. So it was great to have him on the show to chat about it!
  Links from the show Stefan&amp;rsquo;s Social Links  Twitter LinkedIn Github  Other links from the show  Stryker.NET (ie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 17: TDD with Ian Cooper</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0017-tddwithiancooper/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0017-tddwithiancooper/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Ian Cooper to chat about Test Driven Development (TDD)! We discussed pain points that a lot of people hit when attempting to do TDD, and how to avoid them.
  Links from the show Ian&amp;rsquo;s Social Links  Twitter LinkedIn Github  Other links from the show  Ian&amp;rsquo;s Presentations on Github Ian&amp;rsquo;s talk - &amp;lsquo;TDD - Where did it all go wrong?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 16: Learning and Self Development with James World</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0016-learningwithjamesworld/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0016-learningwithjamesworld/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by James World to chat about learning! We covered an incredible amount in this episode - from certifications, to books and reading, interviews, what it means to be a senior developer, and much much more!
  Links from the show James&#39; Links  Twitter LinkedIn (please include a note in your connection request so you stand out from the recruiter bots! Maybe a book recommendation?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 15: C#9 Source Generators with Jason Bock</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0015-sourcegeneratorswithjasonbock/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0015-sourcegeneratorswithjasonbock/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Jason Bock to chat about the new C#9 source generators! Writing code that writes code! We covered a ton of content, covering Source Generators, the Compiler API, Syntax Trees, Semantic Models, Expression Trees, and much much more!
  Links from the show Jason&amp;rsquo;s Links  Twitter Blog Github YouTube  Jason&amp;rsquo;s books  Metaprogramming in .NET Applied .NET Attributes CIL Programming: Under the Hood of .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 14: Spectre Console and Cake with Patrik Svensson</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0014-patriksvensson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0014-patriksvensson/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Patrik Svensson, creator of both the Cake Build System, and a .NET library called Spectre.Console. We mostly chatted about the Spectre Console library, which adds AMAZING functionality to .NET console apps (grid, charts, images, and much more!). We also touched on Cake and Cake Frosting.
  Links from the show Patriks links  Blog Twitter LinkedIn  Links from the show  Spectre.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 13: DevOps with Dushyant</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0013-devopswithdushyant/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0013-devopswithdushyant/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by good friend and ex-colleague, Dushyant Priyadarshee to chat about devops! We covered a lot of ground, from what devops is, to infrastructure as code deployments, to exams and certifications! Dushyant is a Senior Platform Engineer at NewDay.
  Links from the show Dushyant&amp;rsquo;s links  Blog Twitter LinkedIn NewDay (workplace)  Other links from the show  Terraform Terraform CDK Pulumi Bicep Terratest TFSec Azure DevOps Azure ARM Templates Azure DevOps &amp;ldquo;name&amp;rdquo; Twitter Poll GitHub Actions Microsoft Learn Microsoft Exams/Certifications MeasureUp  DevTip links  Daily Coding Problem The Phoenix Project book The Unicorn Project Notion  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 12: Kentico Kontent Headless CMS and JAMStack - with Matt Nield</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0012-mattnield/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0012-mattnield/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by good friend Matt Nield, who also co-runs the .NET Oxford user group with me. We chatted about the Kentico Kontent headless CMS, static websites and the JAMStack - plus much more!
  Links from the show Matt&amp;rsquo;s links  Matt&amp;rsquo;s website Matt on Twitter  Kentico  Kentico main website Kentico Kontent Kentico Xperience (previously Kentico EMS): Kentico Kontent extended 3-month trial offer from Matt  Other links from the show  JAMStack HttpClient Interceptor LINQPad Matt&amp;rsquo;s YouTube video on using Kentico Kontent with LINQPad Statiq .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 11: LINQPad with Joseph Albahari</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0011-linqpad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0011-linqpad/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Joe Albahari, author of one of my favourite software development tools - LINQPad! This is a tool that I use on a daily basis, and it saves me so much time! So I especially enjoyed chatting with Joe about the many features of LINQPad, his experiences when developing it, and also future plans.
  Links from the show  LINQPad Joe&amp;rsquo;s website Joe/LINQPad on Twitter LINQPad Tips and Tricks blog post series: Part1, Part2, Part 3 Writing a Neural Net from Scratch talk Pushing C# to the limit talk (alarm clock reference) .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 10: F# and Functional Programming</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0010-fsharp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0010-fsharp/</guid>
      <description>In this group episode I was joined by Scott Wlaschin, Isaac Abraham, and Ian Russell - to talk all about F#! This is .NET&amp;rsquo;s functional programming language, and we discussed functional programming, and the benefits of using a functional programming language like F#, whilst also comparing it to other languages like C#.
  Guests&#39; social links  Ian Russell: Twitter, LinkedIn Isaac Abraham: Twitter, LinkedIn Scott Wlaschin: Twitter, LinkedIn  Links from the show  F# for fun and profit (Scott&amp;rsquo;s website) Ian&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Introduction To Functional Programming In F#&amp;rdquo; blog post series Isaac&amp;rsquo;s book: &amp;ldquo;Get Programming with F#&amp;quot; Scott&amp;rsquo;s book: &amp;ldquo;Domain Modeling Made Functional&amp;rdquo; Dan&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Writing More Succinct C#&amp;rdquo; blog post C# code-snippet Dan referred to when talking about using LINQ on a single object Nancy Framework Carter API Endpoints Diamond Kata:  Diamond Kata - TDD with only property-based tests Diamond Kata in F#   Book: &amp;ldquo;Stylish F#&amp;rdquo; by Kit Eason (@kitlovesfsharp) Blog post: &amp;ldquo;Ten reasons not to use a statically typed functional programming language&amp;rdquo; (&amp;ldquo;Like most programmers, I’m naturally conservative and I dislike learning new things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 9: Functional Programming in C# with Simon Painter</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0009-simonpainter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0009-simonpainter/</guid>
      <description>For this very first episode of 2021, I was joined by Simon Painter to talk all about Functional Programming in C#! We spoke about functional concepts, plus terms such as Options, Maybes, and even tried to explain what a Monad is! As usual, there were a few tangents, and we also touched on topics such as React, TDD, and much more!
  Links from the show  Simon&amp;rsquo;s social links:  Twitter Website   Book: Functional Programming in C# by Enrico Buonanno Recording of Simon&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Functional Programming in C# talk (thanks to .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 8: Identity with Christos Matskas</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0008-identitywithchristosmatskas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0008-identitywithchristosmatskas/</guid>
      <description>In this last episode of the year, I was joined by Christos Matskas to talk all about Identity! Christos is the Program Manager for the Microsoft Identity Platform, so obviously the conversation was slightly biased towards AzureAD and B2C as an identity provider - but we also tried to cover some common identity topics, and demystify terminology such as OAuth, OpenID Connect, scopes, claims, and more! We even went a bit off-piste at the end and chatted about public speaking, languages (not programming languages), and even touched on speed reading!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 7: WSL2 with Stuart Leeks</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0006-stuartleeks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0006-stuartleeks/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Stuart Leeks to chat all about WSL2, and his new book, WSL 2 Tips, Tricks, and Techniques! We also covered plenty of other topics, such as public speaking, Windows Terminal, standing desks, and much more! Stuart is a Principal Software Development Engineer at Microsoft.
  Links from the show  Stuart&amp;rsquo;s social links:  Twitter Blog GitHub   THE BOOK! WSL2 homepage Dr Michelle Dickinson:  @NanogirlLabs on Twitter Public Speaking Skills for Quiet People How to Rock the Stage (with Dr James Whittaker)   Stuart&amp;rsquo;s WSL2 .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 6: The DDD Conferences</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0006-ddd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0006-ddd/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by five awesome guests to chat all about the DDD conferences! This was such a fun episode, where we chatted about both organising and speaking at the DDD conferences, plus a few other bits and bats along the way!
  Guests  Jess White Paul Michaels Pete Gallagher Simon Painter Stuart Lang  Links from the show  Wikipedia page about the DDD conferences DDD Day DDD East Midlands blog DDD South West DDD North DDD East Anglia DDD Scotland Event registration for DDD on the 12th Dec Ian Johnson&amp;rsquo;s sketch notes Musical instrument photo taken at end Paul&amp;rsquo;s MiniHack meetup mentioned in intro Dan&amp;rsquo;s DDD-related blog posts:  2017: &amp;ldquo;Fun at DDDSW in Bristol!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 5: Kubernetes with Shahid Iqbal</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0005-shahidiqbal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0005-shahidiqbal/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Shahid Iqbal to chat about Kubernetes. We covered containers in general, Docker, Docker-Compose, Kubernetes, Helm, Istio, and much more! Shahid is a Microsoft MVP and user-group organiser, specialising in Azure and Kubernetes.
  Links from the show  Shahid on Twitter Shahid&amp;rsquo;s blog Kubernetes Azure AKS Google GKE Amazon EKS Helm Istio Project Tye KataCoda &amp;lsquo;Deploying blog on Kubernetes&amp;rsquo; meme ZoomIt Chris O&amp;rsquo;Dell talk on &amp;lsquo;How to get your submission accepted at NDC London&amp;rsquo;  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 4: Pete Gallagher</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0004-petegallagher/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0004-petegallagher/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Pete Gallagher - Microsoft MVP, Pluralsight author, speaker, user-group organiser, and huge fan of IoT devices and STEM. We had great fun chatted for over an hour about various topics - mostly themed around technologies helping kids get into coding - but with many tangents thrown into the mix!
  Links from the show  Pete on Twitter Pete&amp;rsquo;s blog Scratch Tinkercad Microbit Kit MakeCode MakeCode Extensions MakeCode Arcade Raspberry Pi Simulator MX Chip Simulator ML For Kids Lobe AI AZ220 IoT Exam IoT Docs and Learn Sense Hat Simulator MicroBit: MCP23s17 I/O Expander Source Code AstroPi .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 3: Steve Gordon</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0003-stevegordon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0003-stevegordon/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I had a fascinating chat with Steve Gordon. We covered tons of topics - from his experience in being a Pluralsight author, to performance, productivity, organising user-groups, public speaking, audio editing, and much more!
  Links from the show   Steve&amp;rsquo;s social and content links:
 Twitter Blog Pluralsight YouTube    User-group links and mentioned events:
 .NET South East (Steve&amp;rsquo;s user-group) MK.NET meetup with Steve on the 18th Scott Hanselman&amp;rsquo;s talk at .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 2: Derek Comartin - CQRS, MediatR, and more!</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0002-derekcomartin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0002-derekcomartin/</guid>
      <description>In this second episode, I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to welcome Derek Comartin (also known as CodeOpinion) onto the show to talk about CQRS and MediatR! We ended up recording over two different sessions and covered lots of different topics, including functional programming and remote working.
  Links from the show  Derek on Twitter Derek&amp;rsquo;s blog Derek&amp;rsquo;s YouTube channel MediatR language-ext functional C# library Dan&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Writing More Succinct C#&amp;rdquo; blog post Simon Painter&amp;rsquo;s Functional Programming in C# talk LINQPad (from devtips) Dan&amp;rsquo;s LINQPad Tips and Tricks blog post series  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 1: Hello World!</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0001-helloworld/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0001-helloworld/</guid>
      <description>In this very first episode, I introduce the podcast and what it&amp;rsquo;s all about! This is a short 6-minute episode talking about the focus of the podcast, who I am, and also a bit about .NET Oxford.
  Links from the show  Dan&amp;rsquo;s blog Dan on Twitter .NET Oxford .NET Oxford Slack Azure Oxford  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/pages/about/</guid>
      <description>About page coming soon.
For more information about me, see the about page on my blog.
The best way to get in touch with me is via Twitter - my DMs are open.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guest FAQ</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/pages/guest-faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/pages/guest-faq/</guid>
      <description>Ever wondered what&amp;rsquo;s involved when being a guest on a podcast? Below are a few key points that I tend to mention to each guest. I thought I&amp;rsquo;d consolidate them here for quick reference&amp;hellip;
The podcast is not live! I do a lot of editing afterwards, and it&amp;rsquo;s easy to chop bits out whilst editing. If you need to pause and think about how you&amp;rsquo;re going to answer a question - that&amp;rsquo;s fine - I chop that pause out.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
