<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kubernetes on The Unhandled Exception Podcast</title>
    <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/tags/kubernetes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Kubernetes on The Unhandled Exception Podcast</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/tags/kubernetes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Episode 67: Live Panel Discussion at DDD South West 2024</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0067-dddpanel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0067-dddpanel/</guid>
      <description>This was the first episode we&amp;rsquo;ve done which has been recorded live with an audience! It was hosted at the DDD South West conference in Bristol (UK), and I was joined by a panel of speakers. After introductions, I kicked off the conversation with a question about AI - and then we went from there, taking further dev-related questions from the audience.
  Guest bios Carl Sargunar is a web and mobile application developer and technical consultant, Carl also enjoys working with the wider community, helping run the DDDSouthWest free conference and the .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 66: Serverless, AWS, and .NET - with James Eastham</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0066-jameseastham/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0066-jameseastham/</guid>
      <description>In this episode I was joined by James Eastham to initially to chat about AWS and Serverless with .NET&amp;hellip; but we ended up covering a whole lot more! We chatted about OpenTelemetry, Kubernetes, Rust, and our Dometrain courses too!
James Eastham is a Senior Cloud Architect at Amazon Web Services and content creator. He has over 10 years of experience in software, at all layers of the application stack. He has worked in front-line support, database administration, backend development and now works with some of the biggest companies in the world architecting systems using AWS technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
