<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>devops on The Unhandled Exception Podcast</title>
    <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/tags/devops/</link>
    <description>Recent content in devops on The Unhandled Exception Podcast</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/tags/devops/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Episode 81: AI-driven development and DevOps - with Jeffrey Palermo</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0081-jeffreypalermo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0081-jeffreypalermo/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Jeffrey Palermo to chat about AI-driven development and DevOps. We discussed how AI is changing the way we write software, and the importance of having mature DevOps processes in place (eg. good tests, CI pipelines, and specs) before we can properly start leveraging AI to write features in a reliable and consistent way.
Jeffrey Palermo is the host of the Azure &amp;amp; DevOps podcast, Founder and Chief Architect of Clear Measure, a long-time Microsoft MVP, tech speaker, book author, and more!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 71: GitHub Actions - With Scott Sauber</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0071-githubactions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0071-githubactions/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Scott Sauber to chat about GitHub Actions. Before that though, we chatted about the differences between &amp;lsquo;Continuous Integration&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;Continuous Delivery&amp;rsquo;, and &amp;lsquo;Continuous Deployment&amp;rsquo;. Then we delved into the world of GitHub Actions, and how they can be used to automate your workflows.
Scott is a software consultant and primarily does web development using ASP.NET Core and JavaScript. His second passion behind web development is helping teams realize their potential through technical practices (such as CI/CD, IAC, TDD, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 61: Platform Engineering and IaC - with Shahid Iqbal</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0061-platformengineering/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0061-platformengineering/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined for a second time by Shahid Iqbal, this time to chat about Platform Engineering and Infrastructure as Code! We discussed what Platform Engineering means, and also different IaC tools. And Shahid&amp;rsquo;s undying love for Pulumi! 😂
Shahid is a Principal Platform Architect at Auror based in Auckland NZ, and is also an Azure MVP.
   Shahid&amp;rsquo;s social links  Twitter LinkedIn Blog  Links from the show  Terraform Pulumi Past episode where we talked about Kubernetes Episode on OTel with Martin Thwaites Article on Terraform licence change OpenTofu   If you&amp;rsquo;re enjoying the podcast, please remember to subscribe and share this episode with your friends and colleagues!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 49: Cake 🍰 - with Mattias Karlsson</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0049-cake/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0049-cake/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Mattias Karlsson to chat about Cake! Nope, not the food - something even better! Cake is a build orchestration tool where your builds scripts are written in C#. There are tons of addons for most tasks you can think of, and it&amp;rsquo;s easy to write your own. And you can run these all locally just like you would on the build agent. I dread to think how many many days I&amp;rsquo;ve lost when doing CI/CD natively in YAML where I&amp;rsquo;ve had to push to CI/CD, waiting for a build agent to pick it up, just to find that I&amp;rsquo;d got a path or indentation wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 13: DevOps with Dushyant</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0013-devopswithdushyant/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0013-devopswithdushyant/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by good friend and ex-colleague, Dushyant Priyadarshee to chat about devops! We covered a lot of ground, from what devops is, to infrastructure as code deployments, to exams and certifications! Dushyant is a Senior Platform Engineer at NewDay.
  Links from the show Dushyant&amp;rsquo;s links  Blog Twitter LinkedIn NewDay (workplace)  Other links from the show  Terraform Terraform CDK Pulumi Bicep Terratest TFSec Azure DevOps Azure ARM Templates Azure DevOps &amp;ldquo;name&amp;rdquo; Twitter Poll GitHub Actions Microsoft Learn Microsoft Exams/Certifications MeasureUp  DevTip links  Daily Coding Problem The Phoenix Project book The Unicorn Project Notion  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
