<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>devops on The Unhandled Exception Podcast</title>
    <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/tags/devops/</link>
    <description>Recent content in devops on The Unhandled Exception Podcast</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/tags/devops/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Episode 49: Cake 🍰 - with Mattias Karlsson</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0049-cake/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0049-cake/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Mattias Karlsson to chat about Cake! Nope, not the food - something even better! Cake is a build orchestration tool where your builds scripts are written in C#. There are tons of addons for most tasks you can think of, and it&amp;rsquo;s easy to write your own. And you can run these all locally just like you would on the build agent. I dread to think how many many days I&amp;rsquo;ve lost when doing CI/CD natively in YAML where I&amp;rsquo;ve had to push to CI/CD, waiting for a build agent to pick it up, just to find that I&amp;rsquo;d got a path or indentation wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 13: DevOps with Dushyant</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0013-devopswithdushyant/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0013-devopswithdushyant/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by good friend and ex-colleague, Dushyant Priyadarshee to chat about devops! We covered a lot of ground, from what devops is, to infrastructure as code deployments, to exams and certifications! Dushyant is a Senior Platform Engineer at NewDay.
  Links from the show Dushyant&amp;rsquo;s links  Blog Twitter LinkedIn NewDay (workplace)  Other links from the show  Terraform Terraform CDK Pulumi Bicep Terratest TFSec Azure DevOps Azure ARM Templates Azure DevOps &amp;ldquo;name&amp;rdquo; Twitter Poll GitHub Actions Microsoft Learn Microsoft Exams/Certifications MeasureUp  DevTip links  Daily Coding Problem The Phoenix Project book The Unicorn Project Notion  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
