<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cli on The Unhandled Exception Podcast</title>
    <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/tags/cli/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cli on The Unhandled Exception Podcast</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/tags/cli/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Episode 80: Oh My Posh - with Jan De Dobbeleer</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0080-ohmyposh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0080-ohmyposh/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was delighted to be joined by Jan De Dobbeleer to chat about the amazing Oh My Posh! This is something I&amp;rsquo;ve used for years, so it was really great chatting with Jan about it. Oh My Posh is a highly customisable cross-platform prompt engine for any shell. We also chatted about his experiences as an open-source developer.
Jan is a passionate software engineer with a love for creating clean, intuitive, and user-friendly tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 39: Windows Terminal - with Kayla Cinnamon</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0039-windowsterminal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0039-windowsterminal/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was thrilled to be joined by Kayla Cinnamon to chat about the Windows Terminal! I&amp;rsquo;m a huge fan of WT, and use it daily - so it was an honour to have Kayla on to chat about it! Kayla is a Program Manager at Microsoft, Delivering Windows Terminal and Cascadia Code. She&amp;rsquo;s also the Host of Windows Wednesday, and works on the Windows developer experience.
  Kayla&amp;rsquo;s social links  Twitter LinkedIn  Links from the show  Windows Terminal on GitHub Windows Terminal Promo video PoshGit TerminalSplash.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 14: Spectre Console and Cake with Patrik Svensson</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0014-patriksvensson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0014-patriksvensson/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Patrik Svensson, creator of both the Cake Build System, and a .NET library called Spectre.Console. We mostly chatted about the Spectre Console library, which adds AMAZING functionality to .NET console apps (grid, charts, images, and much more!). We also touched on Cake and Cake Frosting.
  Links from the show Patriks links  Blog Twitter LinkedIn  Links from the show  Spectre.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 7: WSL2 with Stuart Leeks</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0006-stuartleeks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0006-stuartleeks/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Stuart Leeks to chat all about WSL2, and his new book, WSL 2 Tips, Tricks, and Techniques! We also covered plenty of other topics, such as public speaking, Windows Terminal, standing desks, and much more! Stuart is a Principal Software Development Engineer at Microsoft.
  Links from the show  Stuart&amp;rsquo;s social links:  Twitter Blog GitHub   THE BOOK! WSL2 homepage Dr Michelle Dickinson:  @NanogirlLabs on Twitter Public Speaking Skills for Quiet People How to Rock the Stage (with Dr James Whittaker)   Stuart&amp;rsquo;s WSL2 .</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
