<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>community on The Unhandled Exception Podcast</title>
    <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/tags/community/</link>
    <description>Recent content in community on The Unhandled Exception Podcast</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/tags/community/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Episode 53: We Are .NET - with Tim Cadenbach and Matthias Jost</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0053-wearedotnet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0053-wearedotnet/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by both Tim Cadenbach and Matthias Jost to chat about the exciting new .NET community - We Are .NET! At its core, it&amp;rsquo;s a community portal aggregating and presenting videos, blogs, twitch, and other feeds of any creator with .NET content. However, it&amp;rsquo;s not just content aggregation though - and is becoming a rapidly growing community.
  Tim Cadenbach Tim is a developer evangelist at Deepl and Microsoft MVP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 6: The DDD Conferences</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0006-ddd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0006-ddd/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by five awesome guests to chat all about the DDD conferences! This was such a fun episode, where we chatted about both organising and speaking at the DDD conferences, plus a few other bits and bats along the way!
  Guests  Jess White Paul Michaels Pete Gallagher Simon Painter Stuart Lang  Links from the show  Wikipedia page about the DDD conferences DDD Day DDD East Midlands blog DDD South West DDD North DDD East Anglia DDD Scotland Event registration for DDD on the 12th Dec Ian Johnson&amp;rsquo;s sketch notes Musical instrument photo taken at end Paul&amp;rsquo;s MiniHack meetup mentioned in intro Dan&amp;rsquo;s DDD-related blog posts:  2017: &amp;ldquo;Fun at DDDSW in Bristol!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
