<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Maui on The Unhandled Exception Podcast</title>
    <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/tags/maui/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Maui on The Unhandled Exception Podcast</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/tags/maui/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Episode 38: .NET MAUI, IoT, and Handy the bionic Arm - with Clifford Agius</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0038-cliffordagius/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0038-cliffordagius/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode, I was joined by &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/CliffordAgius&#34;&gt;Clifford Agius&lt;/a&gt; to chat about both .NET MAUI, and also developing for IoT. (These were separate topics - not specifically IoT on MAUI). Clifford is an airline pilot who&amp;rsquo;s also a freelance .NET developer who regularly blogs and speaks at conferences around the world!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;MAUI (Multi-platform App UI) is a new .NET framework for building multi-platform apps - both mobile (iOS/Android) and desktop (macOS/Windows) using C# and XAML in a single codebase. It also supports Blazor components for those that prefer that over XAML.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Episode 37: Microsoft Build 2022</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0037-build/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0037-build/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Microsoft have just had their annual Build conference - which comes with a whole host of exciting announcements and discussions about hot programming topics in the Microsoft developer space. And each year, I long for a podcast episode to come out straight after Build, overviewing them! Well, this year - this podcast aims to do just that! In this episode, I was joined by both &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/coolcsh&#34;&gt;Scott Hunter&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/gauravseth&#34;&gt;Gaurav Seth&lt;/a&gt; to chat about various topics. Check out the links below for a guide to what we discussed.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
