<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>event-driven-architecture on The Unhandled Exception Podcast</title>
    <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/tags/event-driven-architecture/</link>
    <description>Recent content in event-driven-architecture on The Unhandled Exception Podcast</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/tags/event-driven-architecture/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Episode 51: Brighter - with Ian Cooper</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0051-brighter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0051-brighter/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Ian Cooper to chat about the Brighter and Darker frameworks.
Brighter is a framework for building messaging applications with .NET and C#. It can be used with an in-memory bus, or for interoperability in a microservices architecture allowing out of process messaging via a wider range of middleware transports. And Darker is the query counterpart to Brighter.
Ian is a Senior Principal Engineer at Just Eat Takeaway, frequent public speaker, and organiser of London .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 40: Demystifying Messaging in Azure - with Sean Feldman</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0040-azuremessaging/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0040-azuremessaging/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Sean Feldman to chat all about messaging in Azure! Starting off explaining why you&amp;rsquo;d want to use messaging in your solutions. Then explaining the difference between different types of messaging - eg. pub/sub, event streaming, etc. Then going through discussing all the different Azure services that relate to messaging.
Sean Feldman is a consulting Solutions Architect and an Azure MVP. He likes tinkering with various Azure-related services and is in seventh heaven when cloud and distributed technologies are combined.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 31: MassTransit and Open Source - with Chris Patterson</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0031-masstransit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0031-masstransit/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Chris Patterson to chat about the open-source distributed messaging framework, MassTransit. We also spoke about open-source, event-driven architecture, docker, k8s, testing, Rider, and more!
  Chris&amp;rsquo;s social links  Twitter Github YouTube  Links from the show  MassTransit MassTransit Discord RabbitMQ Azure Service Bus Apache Kafka Azure Event Hub Kubernetes Istio Linkerd JetBrains Rider Visual Studio Live Share JetBrains Code With Me Past podcast episode re.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 26: Event Sourcing and Event Driven Architecture - with Callum Linington</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0026-eventsourcing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0026-eventsourcing/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Callum Linington to chat about Event Sourcing! Events over time are how the world works - so shouldn&amp;rsquo;t we be leveraging that in our architectures? As quite often happens, we also went on one or two tangents, and covered a ton of other related including MediatR, CQRS, F#, DDD, Rx, Redux, and more!
  Callum&amp;rsquo;s social links  Twitter LinkedIn Github  Links from the show  EventStore Apache Kafka Video: Greg Young — A Decade of DDD, CQRS, Event Sourcing MediatR Redux Rx Callum&amp;rsquo;s Liaison library Video: &amp;lsquo;Reaqtor&amp;rsquo; - Endjin&amp;rsquo;s Rx at scale talk at .</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
