<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cms on The Unhandled Exception Podcast</title>
    <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/tags/cms/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cms on The Unhandled Exception Podcast</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/tags/cms/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Episode 69: The Umbraco CMS and Community</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0069-umbraco/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0069-umbraco/</guid>
      <description>In this group episode, I was joined by Carl Sargunar, Lotte Pitcher, Carole Rennie Logan, and Callum Whyte, to discuss the Umbraco community and CMS! We chatted about the amazing community around Umbraco, as well as the features of the CMS itself. It definitely made me want to reach for Umbraco next time I need a CMS!
  Guest bios Carl Sargunar is an independent web and mobile application developer and technical consultant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 12: Kentico Kontent Headless CMS and JAMStack - with Matt Nield</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0012-mattnield/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0012-mattnield/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by good friend Matt Nield, who also co-runs the .NET Oxford user group with me. We chatted about the Kentico Kontent headless CMS, static websites and the JAMStack - plus much more!
  Links from the show Matt&amp;rsquo;s links  Matt&amp;rsquo;s website Matt on Twitter  Kentico  Kentico main website Kentico Kontent Kentico Xperience (previously Kentico EMS): Kentico Kontent extended 3-month trial offer from Matt  Other links from the show  JAMStack HttpClient Interceptor LINQPad Matt&amp;rsquo;s YouTube video on using Kentico Kontent with LINQPad Statiq .</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
