<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on The Unhandled Exception Podcast</title>
    <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on The Unhandled Exception Podcast</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language><atom:link href="https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/pages/about/</guid>
      <description>About page coming soon.
For more information about me, see the about page on my blog.
The best way to get in touch with me is via Twitter - my DMs are open.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alternative manual recording method</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/pages/guest-faq-manual-recordings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/pages/guest-faq-manual-recordings/</guid>
      <description>If you prefer not to use Discord and the Craig bot for the recording, then we can manually record audio locally. For example, perhaps there&amp;rsquo;s sensitive content that&amp;rsquo;s NDA at the time of recording, which you&amp;rsquo;d prefer not to be stored on the Craig bot&amp;rsquo;s servers.
I have no strong preference either way to whether we use Discord or manual recordings - as long as everyone in the call is comfortable recording their own audio and transferring the recorded wav to me somehow - Dropbox or OneDrive, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guest FAQ</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/pages/guest-faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/pages/guest-faq/</guid>
      <description>Ever wondered what&amp;rsquo;s involved when being a guest on a podcast? Below are a few key points that I tend to mention to each guest. I thought I&amp;rsquo;d consolidate them here for quick reference&amp;hellip;
The podcast is not live! I do a lot of editing afterwards, and it&amp;rsquo;s easy to chop bits out whilst editing. If you need to pause and think about how you&amp;rsquo;re going to answer a question - that&amp;rsquo;s fine - I chop that pause out.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
