<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>rabbitmq on The Unhandled Exception Podcast</title>
    <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/tags/rabbitmq/</link>
    <description>Recent content in rabbitmq on The Unhandled Exception Podcast</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/tags/rabbitmq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Episode 56: NServiceBus - with Laïla Bougriâ</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0056-nservicebus/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0056-nservicebus/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I had great fun chatting with Laïla Bougriâ about NServiceBus and how it can help with your distributed architecture. From its support for observability (including OTel) and dashboarding, to sagas and pub/sub. Even zombie and ghost messages! (spooky!). And as has been known to happen on this show - we did end up going on a tangent and geeking out about the awesome Jetbrains Rider too!
Laïla is a Solutions Architect and Software Engineer at Particular Software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 51: Brighter - with Ian Cooper</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0051-brighter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0051-brighter/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Ian Cooper to chat about the Brighter and Darker frameworks.
Brighter is a framework for building messaging applications with .NET and C#. It can be used with an in-memory bus, or for interoperability in a microservices architecture allowing out of process messaging via a wider range of middleware transports. And Darker is the query counterpart to Brighter.
Ian is a Senior Principal Engineer at Just Eat Takeaway, frequent public speaker, and organiser of London .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 31: MassTransit and Open Source - with Chris Patterson</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0031-masstransit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0031-masstransit/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Chris Patterson to chat about the open-source distributed messaging framework, MassTransit. We also spoke about open-source, event-driven architecture, docker, k8s, testing, Rider, and more!
  Chris&amp;rsquo;s social links  Twitter Github YouTube  Links from the show  MassTransit MassTransit Discord RabbitMQ Azure Service Bus Apache Kafka Azure Event Hub Kubernetes Istio Linkerd JetBrains Rider Visual Studio Live Share JetBrains Code With Me Past podcast episode re.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
