<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>productivity on The Unhandled Exception Podcast</title>
    <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/tags/productivity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in productivity on The Unhandled Exception Podcast</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/tags/productivity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Episode 78: Goals and time management - with Gui Ferreira</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0078-guiferreira/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0078-guiferreira/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, I was joined by Gui Ferreira to chat about one of my favourite topics - life productivity! Where we talked about goal-setting, time management, and productivity in general. We also chatted a bit at the end about testing and AI.
Guilherme Ferreira, also known as Gui, is a Minimalist Software Craftsman, passionate about simplicity and continuous learning. Gui is a Microsoft MVP for Developer Technologies, a Tech Speaker, a YouTuber, and a .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 73: Upgrade your Brain&#39;s OS - with Rob West</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0073-robwest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0073-robwest/</guid>
      <description>As developers, we&amp;rsquo;re always looking for ways to improve and optimise our code. Yet we often neglect our body&amp;rsquo;s hardware and software. In this episode, I was joined by Rob West, to chat about how we can use mindfulness, nutrition, and exercise to upgrade our brain&amp;rsquo;s operating system. A large part of our discussion was about our ability to focus, why are brains naturally struggle with this, especially in the modern world - and techniques to help us with this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 30: Developer Productivity with (me!) Dan Clarke</title>
      <link>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0030-developerproductivity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unhandledexceptionpodcast.com/posts/0030-developerproductivity/</guid>
      <description>Developer productivity is something I&amp;rsquo;ve been really interested in for quite a few years. So I decided, rather than having a guest on for this topic - it&amp;rsquo;s one I wanted to cover myself. So in this first episode of the year - I&amp;rsquo;ve gone solo, and talk about the things I find have made a big difference to my productivity over the years. Also why I think this term &amp;ldquo;10x developer&amp;rdquo; is a big understatement!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
